Women's labour history interview collection (Sara Diamond interviewer)
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Interviews: sound recordings, 1979; F-67-2; 43 sound recordings
  - Storm, Marjorie, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-37; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-745, Audio reel OBJ-746, Audio cassette OBJ-667)
    Storm, Marjorie; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item72, F-67-item73, F-67-item144.
    - OBJ-667_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-667_sideB.wav
  - Tallman, Eileen, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-38; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-747, Audio reel OBJ-748, Audio cassette OBJ-668, Audio cassette OBJ-669)
    Tallman, Eileen; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item74, F-67-item75, F-67-item144, F-67-item145.
    - OBJ-668_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-668_sideB.wav
    - OBJ-669_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-669_SideB.wav
  - Vaselenek, Eva, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-39; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-749, Audio reel OBJ-750, Audio cassette OBJ-670, Audio cassette OBJ-671)
    Vaselenek, Eva; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item76, F-67-item77, F-67-item146, F-67-item147.
    - OBJ-670_SideA.wav
    - OBJ-670_SideB.wav
  - Waddell, Chris, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-40; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-751, Audio reel OBJ-758, Audio cassette OBJ-672, Audio cassette OBJ-673)
    Waddell, Chris; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item78, F-67-item79, F-67-item148, F-67-item149.
    - OBJ-672_SideA.wav
    - OBJ-672_SideB.wav
    - OBJ-673_SideA.wav
    - OBJ-673_SideB.wav
  - Whisker, Richard and Phyllis, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-41; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-759, Audio cassette OBJ-674, Audio reel OBJ-760)
    Whisker, Phyllis; Whisker, Richard; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item81, F-67-item150.
    - OBJ-674_SideA.wav
    - OBJ-674_SideB.wav
  - White, Bill, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-42; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-761, Audio cassette OBJ-675)
    White, Bill; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item82, F-67-item151.
    - OBJ-675_SideA.wav
    - OBJ-675_SideB.wav
  - Wilson, Elizabeth (Liz), 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-43; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-762, Audio reel OBJ-763, Audio cassette OBJ-676, Audio cassette OBJ-677, Audio cassette OBJ-678, Audio cassette OBJ-679)
    Wilson, Elizabeth; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item83, F-67-item84, F-67-item152, F-67-item153, F-67-item154, F-67-item155.
    - OBJ-676_SideA.wav
    - OBJ-676_SideB.wav
    - OBJ-677_SideA.wav
    - OBJ-677_SideB.wav